appgeeker.com 2019-04-02

# Privacy Statement | AppGeeker

We take your privacy seriously. Please take a moment to read this privacy policy, which discloses the privacy practices of the appgeeker.com. We will not collect any personal information about you without your clear permission. Any personal information which you volunteer to AppGeeker will be treated with the appropriate standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Acts. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to AppGeeker's commitment to protecting your privacy. AppGeeker will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever. Your privacy is a priority at AppGeeker, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

What information do we collect? What do we use it for?

We cooperate with PayPal, SWREG and RegNow to provide you safe and fast e-commerce services. When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers that you might like to hear about. 

How do the 3rd party credit card processors protect customer's information? 

AppGeeker uses secure server hosted by regNow and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us, including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

RegNow

regNow is an advanced secure online payment service for software registration that has been in operation since 1994. AppGeeker Shopping Center uses regNow to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase. 

Anti-malware statement

AppGeeker STRONGLY OPPPOSES all forms of malware. AppGeeker applications will never intentionally jeopardize our customers' privacy or security. All applications are designed to be easily removable from the computer through an uninstall utility. We does not employ the use of reinstallers and avoids all features that may be found in any type of malware. No AppGeeker application is designed to collect any personally identifiable information from any user. AppGeeker applications do not contain, nor are they bundled with, any third party applications (spyware, adware, malware, etc.) that would jeopardize our customers' security or their privacy. 

About cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our website and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.  
You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages. 

Changes to This Policy

Please note that AppGeeker may change this policy from time to time. Any amended policy terms will be posted to our website.
